digitaldirect.co.uk 2007-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Digital Direct

Digital Direct take your privacy rights as a customer seriously. This policy outlines the data we collect from our visitors and how we use it.

Any personal information provided to Digital Direct is used solely by Digital Direct (GB) Ltd, 19 Mather Street, Kearsley, Bolton, BL4 8AT.

**In order to monitor the performance of our site we collect the following information:**  
\- An IP address to monitor site traffic and volume  
\- A session ID to uniquely identify you on our site

**In order to fulfill any orders placed with Digital Direct, we collect the following details:**  
\- Email address & telephone number to contact you regarding the order  
\- Name of Customer  
\- Credit card and delivery address for security fraud checks

**In order to provide a valuable service to our Members we collect the following details:**  
\- Name  
\- Address  
\- Email Address  
\- Buying Preferences to aid navigation and inform them of offers if they so request

**Security**  
When you place orders or access sensitive account information, we offer the use of a secure server.  
The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Legislation, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.

Digital Direct does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to no@digitaldirect.uk.com.

In accordance with the Privacy & Electronic Communications Act passed into law in December 2003, Digital Direct do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses ('spam').  
Digital Direct conform with the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998. 

Should you have any queries with regard our privacy policy then please contact us at privacy@digitaldirect.uk.com

All prices include V.A.T. at 17.5%.  
Copyright © 2007 Digital Direct GB Ltd. All rights reserved. E&OE. V5.3  
Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
